Madam, the sergeant can now smash
Thank you
Ms. Nana Matur, please sit down.
Double degree, bachelor degree in education
Master of Science, impressive
Thank you
Drink of water? Can solve this problem
This is not a snoring, I am suffering from Toray's disease.
Oh? What disease?
Well, this is a nervous system disease, lady.
Sometimes when the nerve signal in the brain is abnormal
Will cause shock
So... how to stop it?
Sir, there is no way.
When I am nervous, it will be worse
Just like now
Do you have these noises when you sleep?
No, my brain is sleeping when I sleep.
But how long can we sleep?
we?
Yes, me and... my tortoise
twenty one
Does it have an effect on eating and drinking?
twenty two
We handled it very well, Mrs.
twenty three
Eating has no effect, drinking water will not work.
twenty four
Ok, Ms. Nana, we will inform you.
Ok, sir, thank you for taking time out of your busy schedule.
Thank you for coming
Ms. Mathur, if you don’t mind, give advice.
Teaching like this can be difficult
You can try to change jobs.
I hope I can understand
Sir, can I ask a few words?
can
Did you know about Toray's disease before today?
No, I don’t understand at all.
what about now?
Now we know
If I can teach the principal and the board some new things
I am sure that I can manage the children, sir.
Thank you
Nana, don't wear black paint, work black.
Why do you just say no, your eyes will be embarrassed, children?
mom
Punjabi clay chicken came, this is the potato ball
Little girl, see what I added?
Carefully marinated minced meat
These "experiments" go to the kitchen of your restaurant to do
This kitchen is my kitchen
Domineering, this kitchen is my kitchen
I will clean my hands before I teach you.
Ms. Mathur
Children will fight because of jealousy
Can't help but laugh
How do they learn?
Madam, I am sure I can let them stop laughing at me.
But laughing with me and laughing
I can work for you.
But first... make sure you don’t make these noises
Sir, actually, even you will have a little...
ignorance
School needs new teacher
At the same time it also needs a new principal
Good day, sir
Title: "My Teacher"
Tiny ants will also fall
However, it can build a wall with sandstone
be quiet
Everyone shuts up
Stand up, Nana
Why do you want to make these noises in class?
Always in this "wow wow"
Also, what little funny things are you doing?
sit down
The ant's persistence gave her strength...
I said, quiet
Listen, tell the truth
Her condition makes other children in the class
Hard to learn normally
- Nana is the same.
- But, sir...
I gave you a notice of withdrawal
There is no reason mentioned above
Maybe she needs a different school
Mrs. Mathur
Goodbye
Dad, I want this.
Nana?
Dad, I...
Please take a chocolate cake
Why don't you understand? Suha
Nana needs a special school.
Nana needs an ordinary school.
Ordinary life
She is a normal girl, Prabhaka
normal? Are these convulsions normal?
Because of these noises, she has been very shy
Is she ashamed or do you feel ashamed?
Are you forgetting why we are apart?
Listen, Nana is my daughter after all.
Yes, she is, when she needs you these years.
Where have you been?
Little sister, my father is here.
I feel uncomfortable
Say at least in the past
Can I say hello and goodbye at the same time?
Well, of course, come on.
Go first, I will come right away, don't pull me.
Please, Vigny.
How uncomfortable, okay?
Is a cold
she's fine
I am nervous, what else can I have?
Holding
I have friends at the bank, this is the job for you.
open to take a look
Nana, part-time animator
This is not work
I am working part time because I need time.
Go to the teacher's vacancy
I have been looking for five years now.
With this disease...
Pooh, you don’t have much pancakes.
Oh yes
Why don't you say a few words?
Nana, the flour in the refrigerator is much
Just take a look, ok?
Sorry, my hand is dirty, I will see it later.
How much can you earn when you are a teacher?
Dad, you are at school or college.
Is there a favorite teacher?
Of course there is
Do you remember his salary?
Forgot, Dad.
You will never remember
Yes, I am not going to...
Then why do you have a master of science?
Bachelor of Education
But doing comics at home?
Hello, wait a moment...
Little girl, phone at St. Tick High School
Is her hand not dirty?
No, sir, that is my dog.
It’s time to have lunch
Ok, no problem, I will go, when?
At eleven tomorrow, I will arrive, sir.
But the teacher you are looking for
May teach less than one semester
No, sir, I have no problem, I will arrive.
Ok, ok, of course, sir.
what happened?
I have a job.
No, no, impossible, little girl
Life is really a turnaround.
I have a job.
(St. Tick High School)
妳's qualifications are very good, Ms. Mathur
Thank you
And I also appreciate the spirit of jealousy.
We are willing to give you a chance
Thank you, sir, thank you.
Also because we urgently need a teacher
Mr. Wadia, please...
You can start
Do you have Tourette's disease?
Yes
I want to know
妳說妳 has been rejected by 18 schools
Even St. Tick’s secondary school refused you five times.
I am curious, I am suffering from this disease.
Why do you want to be a teacher?
Because that chair
Do you want to be a principal?
Oh, no
Like the 18 schools that rejected me.
When I was a student
Also abandoned by twelve schools
This school is the same as my lucky number.
Are thirteen
I am sitting in front of you and want to be a teacher.
Because twenty-two years ago
Mr. Khan sitting in the chair
Give me the most important lesson in my life.
Who is this evil?
Kind compatriots, let me leave alone
For my sake, please stay here to listen to Anthony...
Congratulations on this wonderful performance
Tell me now, in this performance
Have you heard some strange noises?
Who made these noises? Please stand on the stage
Come on stage immediately
What is your name?
Nana Matur, teacher
Can you please stop fighting?
I can't do it, teacher.
why?
I am suffering from Toray's disease
I have never heard of it.
Teacher, this is a nervous system disease.
For some reason, I am like an electric shock.
Are there any other students who are right?
They laugh at me and tease me
What about the teacher?
They drove me out of the class
Tell me, what can we do for you?
How can we help?
Just like treating other students
Treat me, please.
my child…
Here is the school
Everyone comes here to learn
But today you gave us a lesson.
I promise to the St. Tick High School
We will treat you like other students.
Ok?
Let's go back
General teacher teaches knowledge
Excellent teacher teaches people to understand
If he is better
Then he will tell you how to use it
Some teachers will also inspire us
For me, Mr. Khan is the kind of teacher.
Mr. Khan inspired us all
Come to me, he has always been a teacher.
Sir, I assure you that I will not let you down.
I came to the world to be a teacher.
Ms. Mathur, can you control these sounds?
I mean
I have never seen a teacher with a speech defect.
Toray's disease affected my expression
But it didn't affect my intelligence
Come with me, Ms. Mathur
Thank you, sir, thank you, madam.
The choice is terrible
Good morning, teacher
National Science Fair?
St. Tick High School has been the champion for the past two years.
This is thanks to Teacher Wadia.
Head of our science team
This year we are looking forward to completing the hat trick
Class 9A
The smartest student in the school
All gifted students are from here
Sir, I was in class 9C at the time.
Mr., class F?
Didn't there be Class F before?
Well, this is an initiative attributed to the right to education.
We are developing
Only fourteen children
Just fourteen?
But why is the classroom empty?
Because the previous teacher is on vacation
Permanent leave
With the truth, I urgently need a teacher.
That's why I am looking for a half-semester class.
I saw energy in my body.
I am also willing to take risks
Under normal circumstances
I won't give this job.
But this is a special case
This class is the same, 9F
I want to think about it.
Sir, I have already considered it.
I really want this job.
I will not let you down
They are a group of children
How bad can you still be?
Ms., do you want to teach class 9F?
Yes what's the matter?
Nothing, full of good
Ms
9F class is upstairs, here is walking
I know
This is too dirty, how can they not clean up?
Who will tell Shamlar?
Let him clean us once a day
The echo here is great, classmates
Is there smoke?
How can I call these things?
You play your brain game, I tease my mouse
I have smoke
When did you start smoking?
Don't smoke, I just help Cram hold
Brother, the police made a surprise attack yesterday.
We have to slip
They will catch you sooner or later, brother
How can I call them?
Wadia and Parilla
No, are you crazy?
My mouse will die from shock
Oh, don't smoke next to my mouse.
You will be like ruining your own lungs
Also ruined them
Lavender, do you want to bet?
That stuttering idiot will live a day
Who told you that she is a stutter
The hired employee, Shamlar
Brother, Shamlar can get the letter
Don't believe his words.
Give you
If you don't smoke
Why are you doing this?
give me
Give you
Tamana, what would you buy if you bet?
Buy a new color nail polish
Catalina Cuff
What does she use?
Girl
What the world wants to see is the finger of Catalina Kraft.
Who is your finger going to see? Auntie
Ok, everyone listens to me.
Ten loses eleven, I gamble on Ms.
Ten loses sixteen, if she stays for a week
Who is going to do some action?
This odds can be accepted
- how much is it?
- This is ten pieces.
This is gambling, not begging
Hold this thirty and close your mouth
My twenty
Ms. Jieba’s bureau, don’t you want to bet?
Don't push me
Then stand that turtle.
- Go quickly.
- Go hurry.
I am young and famous.
What do you use, not to mix with me later?
Classmates, I am your new teacher.
Nana Matur
What to say?
It’s not just in the classroom or in school that is called education.
So whenever you need me,
This is my number
Sorry
Teacher... whenever?
Oh, we must respect women.
Good "female...female"
Know when you name
Ati Xu
To
It is me, teacher
Ashwin
At, at, at
Arundati
To, teacher
Kram
Hey, come, teacher
Am I correcting it?
Looks like the starting point name
You are more interested in my convulsions.
So we might as well start with this.
I am suffering from Toray's disease
This is a nervous system disease
When the nerve signaling in our brain is abnormal
Will bring a little surprise like this
Any questions about my Toray's disease can be asked
Teacher, what is the ringing tone of the phone?
Let me tell you...
One, two, 嗝, 嗝, 嗝...
Three, four, 嗝, 嗝, 嗝
Classmate, my mouse these days
Will also make the same sound
Do you think they have also got Right's disease?
Yeah, very likely
Teacher, have you heard the mouse how to sing?
How did you stop?
This is really like me, very accurate
The only difference is...
You can stop it at any time.
But you can't influence me.
You all know how long I can stay and have a gamble.
And why other people are not waiting
But what you don't know is that I am here.
Not to give up
I am here for teaching.
Lavender
This is my hundred
I am going to stay, I am also making a bet.
Holding
a real gambler, say one thing
Will not go back on odds
Is your rap sing over?
Can I start class?
Teacher, this is just the beginning.
To stay, you have to stand up
Get up now
That's it
She won't leave easily
Don't stare, brother
She is not in our circle
She is the leader of class 9A.
- I am also a leader of the 9F class.
- what?
- What can I stare at, brother?
- that's true
Hey, class F, waste wood, pass the ball.
What happened, brother?
Why do you want to beat people?
You didn't see what he made the ball.
Compared to what you are facing now
This is not bad.
Ati Xu
Oh...oh...
Stop immediately, stop
Stand up, stand up
Teacher, see what they poked the ball into.
Don't worry, teacher, there is no blood on the ball.
You see
You, the principal's office
Ok, teacher
Go, go
go
Madam, it’s too early.
Well, I have to go to the library to get some books, so...
So, I’m going to keep going.
Shamlar, I want to ask you something.
What is the 9F class?
Who are those children?
I saw the playground, ladies.
There used to be a government municipal school.
There is a sewer after crossing the highway
There is a slum nearby
Things are all very good
Garbage discharged into the sewer
Slum children go to municipal schools to go to school
Then one day
They know that the school is built on rented land.
The future of these children is also precarious
So the management of St. Tick’s secondary school found the city government.
The government has proposed a regulation called "the right to education"
Therefore, students of the municipal high school
Became a student at St. Tick High School
That land is now the playground of St. Tick High School.
9F class children
Is the last of those slum children
The parents of the fourteen children
Is there no problem with this difference?
Their parents have bigger problems to worry about, ladies
Like three meals a day
There are also questions about queuing for water.
Madam, the children of the slums at first tried to find ways
To integrate into these children
But these children have never accepted them.
Now even the teacher can't help much.
So now these slum children are very rebellious
In the past seven months, you are the eighth teacher.
go to hell
What happened?
- Ok
- what
- What is the answer?
- three
Hey, yeah, listen, what to say? what? what?
(Are you lonely?)
(Please dial the hotline)
Do you feel me? brothers
No, I didn't send any message, you made a mistake.
Not bursting?
The solution is two
a homogeneous mixture of more or more substances
Lemonade, soda and water
Some examples of solutions
If 9F class is so interesting
Natasha, you can join them.
Sorry, teacher
So can you accommodate students in Class 9F?
Sir, they are not that bad.
I don't know if they can accommodate me.
For reference only, the book is not in the ninth grade syllabus.
I told you, Ms. Mathur.
They don't belong here
Oh, because they endure these, I am really sorry.
The principal also agreed that they should be dropped out of school.
Yes
Sir, this is really too embarrassing.
In fact, I want to explain in the chemistry class.
How does liquid nitrogen spread?
I am really sorry, I didn’t expect it to explode.
I am really sorry, sir.
Have nothing to do with them
What do you want to prove? Ms. Mathur
Do you think we are all fools?
The whole school should be
Is a 9F class smoked?
Go back to class and walk away
Ms. Mathur, we all know
This is what they do
I also know
I am still protecting them.
Yes, sir
Like you said
We all know this prank
Maybe they did it
But sir, what they did
Need planning, foresight, and intelligence
Sir, I believe...
If we can find a way
Use this energy correctly
They will one day make Saint Tick High School proud
I assure you, sir.
This dream is out of reach, Ms. Mathur.
They don't belong here, they have never done it before.
Can't do it
They will do it, sir.
Maybe it’s just that our efforts are not enough.
They belong here
Is it challenging me?
They just need some time and effort, sir
How much time?
what?
Set a deadline for the 妳 and 9F classes
Sir, four months, until the final exam
After four months?
Sir, after the exam, the results will prove themselves.
You can do things that seem right
But I am in the next four months
Hope that will not be questioned
Please, sir.
Ok
Thank you, sir, thank you.
The ears are not comfortable, are you?
I used to listen to this at school.
Seventeen years later, I heard this noise again.
From chalk, also from all of you
This is what you have been doing, right?
In school, in life... only howl
What do you want to prove?
Can no one teach you?
Maybe it will surprise you.
But the truth is that no one is interested in teaching you
But I have this interest in teaching you.
Do you know what a great thing about this chalk?
If you fold a little down from above
There will be no more squeaking
a small piece
a small change
This is the difference between "why" and "why not"
Four months late exam
Now, you all have to make a decision.
You are going to make this small change.
Still continue to scream
Meet here at 9 o'clock tomorrow.
If you didn't come,
I will hand over my resignation to the principal at 9:10.
But if you are here
Then we will start again
No "why" but "why not"
Teacher Nana is right.
If we really want to do something
Then pass the final exam
Ms. Jieba is now a teacher?
If you don't have her, we have already dropped out.
So?
Do you want to be the mouse of her scientific experiment?
I don't think we should appear tomorrow.
Why didn't you go to school?
Greek professors are famous because...
American visionary poet...
But away from each other
What is this power called?
Let's start with math today.
As in previous years
Honorary student at St. Tick High School
Setting new standards for academic excellence
I want to ask the Chairman of the Student Council, Mr. Wadia.
Awarded to top students at this moment
Sunidi Prabhakaran, Class 9A
Natasha Cana, Class 9A
Akshe Vemma, Class 9A
Sud Manani, Class 9A
People look for examples in history
But your example is standing in front of you.
Share the stage with these top students
Must be your goal
Students standing on the stage
You need to fulfill the responsibility of this badge
Responsibility as a true St. Tick student
When in doubt, remember
The badge won't compete for you
And you are going to compete for the badge.
Here?
Come in, let's go
Get ready
Today we are here for class.
Isn't that very interesting?
Today we have a new way of name
Ready?
Ati Xu
Kram
Olu
Tamana
Ashwin
Lavender
Lagu
Tara, Safta, Pankaji
Well received, my baby egg, full attendance
Eggs are cooked, eat if you want to eat.
Eggs can go anywhere in the air.
But all of you have received
In terms of mathematics
You didn't read the equation
Just caught the egg
It means you are already a mathematician.
Do we have eggs every day?
Now you only need to learn the equation.
Yes, teacher, only Olu does not understand
She is hiding aside
Not
I can't touch the eggs on Tuesday.
But Olu taught us some physics knowledge.
Olu escaped the path of the egg by action
Force = mass × acceleration
Olu teaches us Newton's law of motion
Walking, sitting, standing, running
We have known all this already.
Now just learn it as an equation
Teacher, if we already know everything
Then why are we wasting time in school?
I can walk in a straight line at any time.
Pankaji, what do you say?
Shouldn't you be in the classroom now?
Yes, sorry, teacher
You don't understand the key point I want to express.
Teacher, we can try everything we want
But we can't make class 9A
We don't want to be
This long badge is just a big show.
What else do you say? When in doubt, remember
Really, teacher, this is all strategy
Generally speaking
I am not the only one with Toride's disease.
Teacher, don't be like this.
Your theory of Tourette's disease is very delicate
But real life is totally different
What are they amazing?
Not a badge?
Not to say the leader badge
As long as you think you can also be your own badge
You only need equal opportunities
What equal opportunity? teacher
I bet, person in class 9A
All let the servants wash their ass
And we got a big size
Have to be a team of 50 meters long
This school and its teacher
Will not let us become the governor
Sir, do you want to see me?
Yes, Mr. Wadia, please sit down.
Ms. Mathur hopes that the 9F class will also qualify for the competition.
Are you kidding? Mr
No
Is this funny? Mr. Wadia
Everyone is eligible to participate in the selection of the leader badge
So 9F class should also have a chance
As St. Tick students, they are also eligible to participate.
Or do you worry that someone in class 9F took the leader?
Ok
Qualification of the badge
Then as the chairman of the student committee
I am not against
But I hope you know
Only in the final exam
Students who get more than 90% are eligible
More than ninety
This is what you want, more than ninety
Ok, sir, thank you.
Ms. Mathur, believe in my 9F class.
It is enough to pass the exam.
Especially considering the way you teach them
Mr. Mathur,
Have you shared her method with you?
Today, on the playground, she took the eggs to class.
What paradox, mathematics
Then she suddenly talked about physics and Newton's law.
Is this a math class, a physics class, or a cooking class?
You are interested in my teaching methods
I am very happy, Mr. Wadia.
Sir, in the real world
Life does not have so many subjects to test us
So Ms. Mathur
It’s both your exam and theirs.
Whether you like it or not
They have to be on the day of the test...
Sitting in the classroom for a test
Don't worry about it.
The 9F class took the 90th day
I will wear the badge on them personally.
Thank you, sir.
Mr. Wadia
Make sure you have more badges that day.
Good day, sir
Listen to me carefully.
I want to separate your brain from disintegration
Hey, you better remember my name.
Even if you are blind, I will plunder you.
This is my game
Grab your belt shorts
We are so hard to make you look so lame
(parent meeting)
Hello, How are you?
Hi
Oman is definitely top
- She really works hard.
- Natasha, well done.
Thank you, teacher
thank you very much
- Hello, madam.
- good Morning
Hashad, is it?
Use snacks
thank you very much
Thank you
What will happen to your parents?
I drank five cups of tea, yes, no parents came.
Oh
Your class is on the playground, isn't it?
Maybe your parents will
I should go to every child's house, isn't it?
Mr. Wadia, in the end...
We finally agreed on certain things.
thank you
Good afternoon, teacher
Keep your eyes open, don't blink, or the money will fly.
This is my twenty
Give you money
Above?
Lavender
Teacher Nana, what are you doing here?
It’s okay.
Why don't you bring a parent to open a parent meeting?
Run, the sliver is coming.
The note is coming, run fast
Hey, Lavender, stop and grab him.
Lavender
Teacher, how come you?
- Tara
- Isn't today a holiday?
holiday? I want to open a parent meeting today.
Did your parents not go?
Mom works in the fishery, my father is not with us.
Sorry, Tara, I don't know...
He didn't die, he just left us.
Go, go, open
Go, go, go...
Right, right...
Teacher, how come you?
Olu
- This is my mom.
- Hello there
Did you drink water on your side?
teacher
Ashwin
This is our stall
Mom, this is the teacher of my school.
Hello there
Teacher, my son is like jackfruit.
The appearance looks very tough, in fact, the heart is very soft.
The child is handed over to you, teacher
Mom, she doesn't know jackfruit.
- Have you ever eaten jackfruit?
- No
Teacher, I am pushing a luggage cart at the airport.
I hope my Safta
The plane that can drive my baggage
So I work hard every day.
Teacher, you are for us.
That is the hope
The whole world is outside the slums
We just want our children
Can do what we have never done before
Kram
Come over, come over... sit down
Lavender, come over, sit here
Ashwin
Lavende came to teach us today.
If you don't mind, I ask a question.
How much did you earn by playing cards?
Eight to twelve months a month
Is it "thousands"?
not bad
I doubt if you can teach us all.
Teacher, don't be kidding.
Seriously, Olu, give me the computer.
Including me, we have a total of fifteen people.
In the case of eight thousand, fifteen people
Earn 120,000
Ok
What if someone is caught?
This is also part of the job
Suppose three of us are caught.
Bail per person 6,350
We still have...
100,000, nine hundred and fifty
Fifteen people
6,700 per person
Teacher, what do you want to say?
These complicated operations you do
Even faster than a computer
However, you are confused in the mathematics curriculum.
Isn't that strange?
Lavender, your talent is different
Use it wisely
Teacher, what can he get from learning?
Maybe a graduate student
But he is already better than those of our slums
Selling detergents from house to house
Graduates earn more
Teacher, I don't want to sell any detergent.
Who asked you to sell detergent?
If you want to gamble, then learn to do something legal.
Not arranging a gamble on the side of the road
But go to the biggest stage in the world... stock market
Learn to bet in the stock market
Who knows? You may be an investment banker.
But for this you have to be prepared
You have to learn
Teacher, he is good at mathematics, talent is different
Then what about the rest of us?
Yes, teacher
Only a small number of children in school have superior intelligence.
The rest is useless?
She is right, teacher
I am convinced that I am an absolute waste wood.
Science, mathematics, and even geography
All are duck eggs
Just like my belly
Kram, you work in a car repair shop.
Why is the car faster in the fourth gear than the second gear?
Teacher, because the friction of the fourth gear is smaller
So run faster
This is physics
Tamana, when?
Apply salt to your fingers?
At the beginning?
Never wiped from the beginning, teacher
Usually at the end
If you wipe it from the beginning
Will seep out of water and become confused
Adding salt can make anything release moisture
This is chemistry
In my opinion, you are the "out of the top"
But there is one more thing you are good at.
Blame one's own situation
Notebook turned to the last page
Spend ten minutes thinking about it.
For yourself, what are you afraid of?
Annoying thing
Then write on that page and start.
Your life stays on this page filled with your fears
But if you can stand them
These realities
Will help you fly, isn't it?
follow me
From today, these fears
Will be your strength, not weakness
Let them go, as they fly freely
- Please take a thermometer
- That infrared
- Sir, that basketball.
- take it
Teacher, we need electronic scales
Who is not comfortable?
That basketball
Behave properly, Akshe
When the ball bounces
Potential energy is converted into kinetic energy and thermal energy
Why can't we experiment with this?
Yes, teacher, the same syllabus.
No?
Why can't we be a little fun?
Children, excellence is not fun
But hard
St. Tick’s expectations for Class 9A are very high
Instead of class 9F
Let's go
Holding a beaker, tightened
Water attracts each other, this is called cohesion
Glass attracts water, this is called adhesion
Brother, between you and Natasha
Is it cohesion or adhesion?
Do you all know?
Once the sailor and the captain did not have a compass
They use their hands like this to determine the direction
Polaris directs them in the direction
What's happening here?
Sometimes I think what Wadia teacher cares about is the score.
And this stupid project
Listen, he also wants us to do our best.
You know
In fact, we can follow him and should feel lucky.
Yes, we are even more fortunate
And they are absolutely more happy
come on…
Thank you teacher, goodbye.
Hi
Hello there
You... don't you go home now?
I am researching a science project
It’s almost done
Want to see it?
- Ok
- Do you want to see it?
- Uh huh.
- Let's go.
Come
Come on soon
Look
Look here, we installed the solar panels here.
Do you know the principle of photovoltaics...
Don't look for trouble, Natasha
They don't understand these
If this is a "solar slum"
They may understand
Akshe
How is Nana’s basketball training?
The solar panels in your model are facing the wrong direction.
Panel should face south
Just like the windows of houses in Greece and Rome in the past
You didn't take into account changes in the position of the sun.
Tilt your solar panel by 19 degrees
Tamana
how did you do that?
I mean where did you learn from?
When playing basketball
Hey, Akshe, the equation can't be solved.
Do you know what went wrong? Is the data wrong?
and many more
I think you should try the Planck formula
Rather than the mass formula
give me
So the "h" in the Planck formula is used as a constant
I tried it, but there is no way to fix it.
Try this
This is a binder
How's it going?
Ok?
what is this?
This is my adhesive
In my bicycle shop, we use it to repair the tires.
Me and my team
Preparing projects for the National Science Fair
Go to other places to repair the tires
Sorry, did I hurt your self-esteem?
You know how to fix holes is a good thing.
No?
Go out
A Ti Xu, are you crying?
What are you bullshit?
Hey, Cram, do you have sunglasses?
Why use it?
The people over there are shining
I am afraid I will flash my titanium eye.
Hey, that light is from the badge of the class.
This must be Wadia to his bride.
Prepared wedding gift
Do you mean that Akshe is the bride of Wadia?
"Sir, sir, how can I get it?
Let my badge shine? "
"Okay, child, wake up every morning.
Kiss once"
"Like my ass"
Ati Xu...Ati Xu
A Ti Xu, don't fight, stop, Ati Xu
You two go back to the classroom
Teacher, why are you standing on his side?
Don't ask, Cram
She is no different from other teachers.
A Ti Xu, I heard what you said to Akshe?
Just like Mr. Wadia’s heart
I want to kick your 9F class out.
You are also ironed to insult Akshe
Then why are you crying:
St. Tick High School will not accept us
Class 9A will not accept us
Don't let me say another word, go back to the classroom.
What else can you say?
You can't even speak normally.
Said two words, played four times 嗝
I don't even know
Is this school or circus?
Ati Xu
Both of you go back to the classroom and go back immediately.
You should slap him, Ms. Mathur.
I have never played students until now.
Don't have a burden, the 9F class is owed
Very happy, you finally realized
Class 9F, they are not suitable for students
You should know, Mr. Wadia.
No bad students, only bad teachers
What happened between the 9F class and me
That's just something between us
I am still their teacher.
They are still my students
- The dishes I want are these, do it well.
- Ms?
Please give me the same
Give me some mashed potatoes
Ms. What do you want?
I need to…
Spaghetti, Italian wide noodle, white sauce
Grilled chicken, don't put pepper, she is allergic
Ok
right? I remember these
- Ok, sir, thank you.
- Thank you.
Your restaurant is getting more and more popular
I looked at the internet and the evaluation was very good.
You should take time
If you have time, then...
Nana, thank you for inviting me.
Not the one I invited you
How is the school? Nana
Okay?
Can we not speak properly?
normal
Dad, this is my normal.
I know that you can't stand my normal.
What is wrong with you?
My fault is like this
I don't need you to order for me.
I don't need you to find me a bank job.
I want to...
calm down
- Birthday Cake
- come on
Ok
Cut the cake first, then let's talk
Blow the candle first
Little girl? No luck
no no
Sorry
It doesn't matter, even if it is a father.
Will also remember this birthday
- Good morning, sir.
- Mr. Wadia, are you ready?
- necessary
- We can't wait.
Ok
good Morning
Ok, Akshe, you start first.
good afternoon
When the sun shines on the photovoltaic material
It converts it into electrical energy
This is the principle of manufacturing solar cells.
Let’s first look at the actual situation.
Then discuss it in detail
So we assume that this halogen bulb is the sun
We can see that
When the sun shines vertically on the glass
The degree of absorption reaches the extreme value
Wow
what happened?
Children, are you okay?
I am very sorry, I am really sorry.
please forgive us
Mr. Wadia, what are you doing?
very sorry
what happened?
Teacher, we don't know
We checked a lot of times
Yes, the teacher is all right.
- Are you sure you have checked everything?
- Yes, teacher, I checked.
Fan, windmill, train, everything
Teacher, I really don't know how this happened.
Who solved the equation I gave yesterday?
Teacher, I solved it.
Ok, show it to me.
What happened, sir... sir?
Hey
This is your thing.
What happened, sir?
teacher
What happened, teacher?
I hope I have not stung your self-esteem.
Ati Xu
Sorry, teacher, I forgot
Teacher, even a hole will not make up
Quiet, Ati Xu
right? teacher
Mr
Ms. Mathur, I think you will be very happy.
The reason is the pride and project of St. Tick High School
Because of your outstanding student
do you know? you are right
There are really no bad students, but there are no medicines to save students.
Who else is involved?
Mr. Wadia, this is impossible...
Kram
Mr
Sir, can you tell me...
Ms. Mathur, get ready for an empty classroom.
Today will be 9F class
The last day of existence in this school
All of you go to the principal's office with me.
It took six months to prepare this project
And the reputation of St. Tick’s High School
Because of your 9F class
Give me a good reason why the 9F class
Still have to stay in school? Even a second
Kram and I did
Why are you running out to take responsibility?
Oh, now you start thinking about us.
Just because you two
What did Nana have experienced?
But first we have to get
Mr. Wadia’s approval
It seems that the principal is going to give you
Long grade badge
A Ti Xu, don't care
Get out of the way
good luck
Sir, how do you want to punish them?
But please don’t order it to drop out
Let them finish the test.
Sir, this is ridiculous.
We are all realistic
Do you think the 9F class can pass the exam?
Sir, I have no answer to these questions.
This is not just a test.
Also about their future
please
Sir, I think this...
They can take the test
But before that, they can't step into the school.
They are now banned from school until the exam begins.
They will have an adverse effect on other students
I…
I understand, sir.
Thank you, sir.
Ms. Mathur
You are a good teacher.
But you are trapped in the wrong class
This is not your fault, it is mine.
The class I arranged for you
I am very worried that we will follow the 9F class.
Also lost a good teacher
Good day, sir
You can take the test
Teacher, starting today
We will learn day and night
- I will make a timetable.
- No need for this.
You are not allowed to enroll before the exam.
In short, I don’t think you need me anymore.
- wish all the best
- Teacher
Ms. Jieba finally got rid of the burden.
A Ti Xu, don’t talk nonsense again.
You thought you were just ruined.
Mr. Wadia’s project?
You also ruined the trust of Teacher Nana.
Ruined 9F class
She just expressed some problems
And you have a problem with your heart.
Maybe my father and Mr. Wadia are right.
Maybe my method is wrong.
Things are now, little girl, look at the opening point
The person you are about is coming, let's deal with it.
Calm, just...
Today she is having a bad time at school.
teacher…
On the terrace that day
Those paper planes we dropped
Teacher, our two papers are blank.
Only two of us did not write anything
You are right, teacher
Our life stopped at the last page
Remember the teacher, let us
Write down our biggest fears
I am really scared, teacher
I am afraid that I will never do it.
As good as 9A class
But what I am most afraid of is
Someone I trust
Anyone
Even myself
Or you
One day will leave us
Teacher, this is my page.
I wrote them all down.
Teacher, I want to fly it.
But the paper plane doesn’t know its direction.
You tell us that the Polaris hangs in the night sky.
Guided vessels
Teacher, I don't know where the starry sky is.
But on earth, you are my "North Star"
Teacher, you are the beacon of my life.
Take an egg as an example to illustrate penetration
I have been back a few days early, you can go to study.
When lightning strikes, first see the lightning, then hear the sound
Because light travels faster than sound
Teacher, the light went out to travel again.
Two ratios, five to ten and sixty to one hundred two
You are reading a book, where do you look?
What are you doing?
Hurry and learn
Go out and go out
- I just…
- Go in
Brother, my head is about to explode.
I am the same, buddy.
A Ti Xu, if we have tested
Teacher Nana has no face.
A Ti Xu, can you look at the rear tires too?
I feel that I am not angry enough.
The exam is getting closer and closer, you seem to have no pressure.
Examination of science and mathematics exams
Want it?
Ok
Lagu
Tara
Godsend comes
Tomorrow's exam paper
right here
A Ti Xu, are you crazy?
You have a problem.
Are you crazy?
I am not for me alone.
If we take a test, Nana’s teacher will be finished.
So, are we going to win like this?
Cheating?
If Nana teacher knows...
Who will go to talk to Teacher Nana?
I don't say, you don't say
We all know how many opportunities we have.
Am I for myself?
I am for all of us.
Also for Teacher Nana
A Ti Xu, you have no medicine to save, crazy.
She will test
I am very happy that you can take me.
Start answering questions now
Sir, this paper...
This volume is absolutely different.
It’s okay.
I wish all the best tomorrow.
teacher
Stop answering
Don't write, it’s time.
By the time, give me...
- How is the test?
- not bad
teacher…
Very good, very good
You wrote this, what did you write?
Teacher, don't worry
We filled in all the space
We can all pass the exam, don't worry
determine?
I am over
Congratulations, brother, I have passed.
Introducing St. Tick High School
This year's new gifted student... Miss Olu
- No, I don't know.
- Brother, Olu is the top of the school.
Thank you
Where is Cram?
I do not know how it happened
I actually passed.
- Congratulations, Kram...
Excuse me, sir.
I taught for twenty years.
I know that students cheated.
They can get away with it
But how can they become gifted students?
And only science and mathematics
Ms. Mathur's class, magic?
Sir, they did learn very seriously.
Still cheated seriously
Sir, that's the answer.
But there is no answer process
If there is a process, it is not an outline teaching.
How do they know the answer? no one knows
This situation is only the same
Knowing the questions and answers is possible
I know that my teaching methods are not very disciplined.
But this does not mean that students in class 9F cheated.
Mr. Wadia, there are many solutions to a problem.
Why is your method only?
And the method of writing into the outline is correct.
Ms. Mathur, the exam papers
Atisch and Kram find Shamlar
Have a leaked test paper
This is a way for you to hand over the 9F class.
Go out
Ms. Mathur
Your students are now firewood, and later
Mr., Class 9F is the cancer that rots in St.
Mr. Wadia
Pay attention to your words
You are talking about students at St. Tick High School.
No longer, Ms. Mathur
Tomorrow, at the rally, they will be expelled from school.
儆效尤
St. Tick High School is not a school for swindlers
Sir, I believe my students are not cheating.
I think I have heard enough.
You can go now
teacher
Teacher, we did get the test paper.
But I swear, teacher, we definitely have no cheating
Teacher, what do you say?
Why don't you marry us?
Because I know that you are not cheating.
Otherwise you all
Will become a gifted student like Aolu
All in all... it won't change my mind
Teacher, this is our problem.
Teacher, we are your students first.
Second is the St. Tick High School.
Suha and Pooh told me
It happened at school today.
You must be very happy
I will not be a teacher again.
Dad, you are here.
Is it for me to find a bank job?
Nana, I will delay me.
Dad, do you pretend that you are not tired?
Who are we cheating?
Each other is our own
What do you think, Dad?
Our life is when you want to come
Want to go and leave?
Dad, are you abandoning us, remember?
You left us, don't come back now.
You know for any parent
What is the most important thing for a father?
Able to solve any problem, family
Childic
I still can't cure your right syndrome.
I want to cure it
Dad, don't need this
This is me
I will continue this way.
listen
No matter what happens at school tomorrow
You don't have to prove anything to anyone
I have seen you for those children.
What have you done?
I can never do this for you.
You stand by them
I am proud of you
teacher
What are you thinking?
too bad
This year we cannot participate in the National Science Fair.
But we have a bigger victory, teacher
After all, we kicked the 9F class out of school.
we?
Yes, I mean this is not what you want?
So I did this
I let Shamlar take the wrong test paper.
I found Ati Xu and Kram
So the people in class 9F are all wrong.
Then take the exam
Even if you don’t take it, who cares?
At least they were kicked out of St. Tik High School.
Teacher, you saw it too.
The length badge is still left in class 9A.
I assure you that we have got the 9F class this year.
Next year we will also win the National Science Fair
I am going to class first.
Everyone knows what the 9F class is doing.
Is absolutely intolerable
We are unanimous
Class 9F will no longer be part of St. Tick High School
Next, please speak to Mr. Wadia.
When I was young
I feel that being a teacher is the hardest thing.
Taught for twenty years, I know
Be a student
Even more difficult
If a student has learned the wrong knowledge
It is impossible to score
If the teacher teaches the wrong, he will not lose points.
Teach easy
It’s hard to learn
We always want to teach others something
I also want to teach something in class 9F.
Even though they are for St. Tick High School
Not so good
Do you know how easy it is to do this?
I am very easy...
I leaked the wrong test paper to Shamlar.
So the 9F class knows
Are wrong topics
Then they will take a test
Not that they want to fail
But I want to make them fail
Ms. Mathur, class 9F, please come to the stage.
Let's go
No matter how difficult it is to teach
There are always teachers who teach students in an easy-to-understand way.
Ms. Mathur, later to honor
Mr
(gifted students)
Ms. Mathur, you are right.
No bad students, only bad teachers
Teacher...teacher
Sir, I don’t think it’s your leaked test paper.
Ms. Mathur, I don’t think you are
Broken the classroom window
I think our scoring problem has not been resolved.
We still need to finish
Three wins at the National Science Fair
Teacher, maybe not as good as your project.
But I swear some parts we used.
From real cars
The equation in the syllabus has not changed.
But the equation between the children has changed.
Even have some new equations
Just like me, everyone is and
They made friends with Tori's disease
I don't know what exactly is Rightel's disease.
Is it convulsions, or the way we look at life?
Of course, it depends on what we think
Because of the difference between "why" and "why not"
It’s a difference
Today, I am retiring from St. Tick High School.
It took twenty years to try to solve this problem.
Twenty-five years
Make sure no one hears me snoring
(We will miss you)